1.

CREATE TABLE Users
(
	title VARCHAR2(10) NOT NULL,
	first_name VARCHAR2(20) NOT NULL,
	last_name VARCHAR2(20),
	user_id  VARCHAR2(15) PRIMARY KEY,
	email VARCHAR2(30) UNIQUE,
	password VARCHAR2(40) NOT NULL,
	dob DATE NOT NULL,
	mobile_no NUMBER(10) UNIQUE,
	flag NUMBER(2) DEFAULT 0
);

INSERT 	INTO Users VALUES('Ms','Huma','Khan','huma_1','humak.1995@gmail.com','76edfb58711812f62cc34793ef96bfee','20-MAR-1994',7351885781,0)
INSERT 	INTO Users VALUES('Mr','Anshul','Gupta','anshul_1','anshulgupta69.ag@gmail.com','9c48017b95dfd5200e4c95df355b13a0','01-AUG-1995',9760900282,0)
INSERT 	INTO Users VALUES('Mr','Manan','Jindal','manan_1','mjindal1393@gmail.com','8047c28b8f2f8e4117dfcbde7c70d7e3','08-AUG-1994',9634236780,0)
INSERT 	INTO Users VALUES('Mr','Ankit','Kumar','ankit_1','2012ankitkmr@gmail.com','855832ee6f8774323af3316081431769','31-AUG-1995',8699573668,0)
INSERT 	INTO Users VALUES('Ms','Srija','Baskaran','srija_1','bsrijabaskaran@gmail.com',' 6c0a3e1e925996c829ef5b4d39e1aed2','23-AUG-1995',9940214990,0)
INSERT 	INTO Users VALUES('Ms','Geetika','Kagdiyal','geetika_1','geetika.kagdiyal@gmail.com','bb3944332c24b5f5ec6dad998adab8d3','14-OCT-1994',8006028537,0)
INSERT 	INTO Users VALUES('Mr','Murali','Krishna','murali_1','monapatimurali@gmail.com','844c70702cf0ae2bbe193e16eef1827f','10-JAN-1996',8800574312,0)
INSERT 	INTO Users VALUES('Mr','Anurag','Chaudhary','anurag_1','anurag940948@gmail.com',' 37f9949f1e71263d818ec596894e4290','06-AUG-1996',9910900587,0)
INSERT INTO Users VALUES('Mr','Ankit','Kumar','admin','2012ankitkmr@gmail.com','192023a7bbd73250516f069df18b500','31-Aug-1995',9412478451,1);


2.

CREATE TABLE Address
(
	user_id  VARCHAR2(15) PRIMARY KEY REFERENCES Users(user_id) ,
	address1 VARCHAR2(30) NOT NULL,
	address2 VARCHAR2(30) NOT NULL,
	area VARCHAR2(15) DEFAULT '-',
	state VARCHAR2(30), 
	zipcode NUMBER(6) REFERENCES Zipcode(zipcode)
);


INSERT INTO Address values('huma_1','32 Pinjora','Malhipur Road','Pinjora','UP',247001)
INSERT INTO Address values('anshul_1','1/7228-E','Shivaji Park','New Delhi','Delhi',110032)
INSERT INTO Address values('srija_1','109 8th block','Mogappair West','Mpgappair','Chennai',600037)
INSERT INTO Address values('anurag_1','House no. 1','Pooran nagar','Unnao','UP',209801)
INSERT INTO Address values('murali_1','Tulasi Krishna','G-4 Santhapeta','Santhpeta','Andhra Pradesh',523001)
INSERT INTO Address values('manan_1','1412B','New Shivpuri','Shivpuri','UP',110026)
INSERT INTO Address values('ankit_1','60 Tharputha','Raipur Road','Raipur','UP',283203)
INSERT INTO Address values('geetika_1','1321 Sector 49B','pushpak complex','Chandigarh','Chandigarh',160047)


3.

CREATE TABLE Zipcode(
zipcode NUMBER(10) PRIMARY KEY,
city VARCHAR2(15) NOT NULL
)

INSERT INTO Zipcode values(110032,'Delhi')
INSERT INTO Zipcode values(110026,'Hapur')
INSERT INTO Zipcode values(247001,'Saharanpur')
INSERT INTO Zipcode values(160047,'Chandigarh')
INSERT INTO Zipcode values(283203,'Firozabad')
INSERT INTO Zipcode values(523001,'Ongole')
INSERT INTO Zipcode values(600037,'Chennai')
INSERT INTO Zipcode values(209801,'Unnao')


4.

CREATE TABLE Department(
dept_id varchar2(10) PRIMARY KEY,
dept_name varchar2(50),
description varchar2(200)
);

INSERT INTO Department VALUES('D001','Electronics','It contains products related to Electronics');
INSERT INTO Department VALUES('D002','Clothes','It contains products related to Clothes');
INSERT INTO Department VALUES('D003','Health and Beauty','It contains products related to Health and Beauty');
INSERT INTO Department VALUES('D004','Sports and Leisure','It contains products related to Sports and Leisure ');


5.

CREATE TABLE Category (
category_id varchar2(10) PRIMARY KEY,
dept_id varchar2(10) REFERENCES Department(dept_id),
category_name varchar2(50),
description varchar2(200)
);


INSERT INTO Category Values('C001','D001','Cameras','This Category contains products related to Cameras');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C002','D001','Computers, Tablets and Laptop','This Category contains products related to Computers, tablets and Laptops');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C003','D001','Mobile Phone','This Category contains products related to Mobile Phone');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C004','D001','Sound and Vision','This Category contains products related to Sound and Vision');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C005','D002','Women Clothing','This Category contains products related to Women Clothing');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C006','D002','Women Shoes','This Category contains products related to Women Shoes');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C007','D002','Women Hand Bags','This Category contains products related to Women Hand Bags');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C008','D002','Men Clothing','This Category contains products related to Men Clothing');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C009','D002','Men Shoes','This Category contains products related to Men Shoes');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C010','D002','Kids Clothing','This Category contains products related to Kids Clothing');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C011','D002','Kids Shoes','This Category contains products related to Kids Shoes');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C012','D003','Makeup','This Category contains products related to Makeup');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C013','D003','Eyes','This Category contains products related to Eyes');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C014','D003','Skin','This Category contains products related to Skin');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C015','D003','Body','This Category contains products related to Body');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C016','D004','Sportswear','This Category contains products related to Sportswear');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C017','D004','Accessories','This Category contains products related to Accessories');
INSERT INTO Category Values('C018','D004','Gymwear','This Category contains products related to Gymwear');

6.

CREATE TABLE Product (
product_id varchar2(10) PRIMARY KEY,
category_id varchar2(10) REFERENCES Category(category_id),
pic_id varchar2(50),
dept_id varchar2(10),
Product_name varchar2(100),
unit_price number(10,2),
quantity number(10)
);

INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P101','C012','fitme.jpg','D003','Maybelline New York Fit Me Matte + Poreless Foundation',495.00,50 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P102','C012','lakme.jpg','D003','Lakme 9 to 5 Complexion Care CC Cream ',299.00,50 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P103','C012','Lagirl.jpg','D003','L.A. Girl Pro Conceal HD',595.00,50 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P104','C013','kajal.jpg','D003','Maybelline New York Eye Studio Lasting Drama Gel Eyeliner  Black',525.00,50 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P105','C013','pallette.jpg','D003','Maybelline New York The 24K Nudes Palette',925.00,50 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P106','C013','mascara.jpg','D003','Maybelline New York Volume Express Hyper Curl Mascara ',325.00,50 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P107','C014','suns.jpg','D003','VLCC Clear Tan Fruits Face Pack ',125.00,50 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P108','C001','1.jpg','D001','Nikon Black Camera',999.00,50 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P109','C002','2.jpg','D001','Nikon Red Camera ',740.00,50 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1010','C001','4.jpg','D001','DSLR Camera ',840.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1011','C001','5.jpg','D001','DSLR Camera ',980.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1012','C003','6.jpg','D001','SanDisk SDHC Card 8GB  ',650.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1013','C003','8.jpg','D001','SanDisk Extreme Card 16GB  ',730.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1014','C005','cloth3.jpg','D002','Van Heusen White Dress ',740.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1015','C005','cloth4.jpg','D002',' Van Heusen Women's Regular Fit Dress  ',600.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1016','C005','cloth5.jpg','D002','Van Heusen Women's Regular Fit Dress  ',680.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1016','C005','cloth6.jpg','D002','Vero Moda Women's Solid Sleeveless High Neck   ',850.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1017','C005','cloth7.jpg','D002','Vero Moda Women's Solid Sleeveless Loose Fit V Neck Casual dress   ',950.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1019','C016','sp3.jpg','D004','Griffel Solid Men's Track Suit ',799.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1020','C017','sp4.jpg','D004','Bsquare Snapback Cap  ',240.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1021','C018','sp5.jpg','D004','Alan Jones Solid Men's Black Track Pants ',539.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1022','C018','sp6.jpg','D004','Maniac Solid Men's Dark Blue Track Pants ',576.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1023','C018','sp7.jpg','D004','Lotto Solid Men's Grey Track Pants ',499.00,100 );


INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1024','C008','men1.jpg','D002','Black printed casual shirt ',740.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1025','C008','men2.jpg','D002','Green and black woven printed casual shirt ',600.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1026','C008','men3.jpg','D002','Off-white and navy blue printed casual shirt ',680.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1027','C008','men4.jpg','D002','Blue solid formal shirt  ',850.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1028','C008','men5.jpg','D002','Brown and navy blue checked formal shirt ',950.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1029','C008','men6.jpg','D002','Black and grey checked formal shirt ',550.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1030','C008','men7.jpg','D002','Blue and white checked casual shirt ',875.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1031','C008','men8.jpg','D002','White, pink and blue checked casual shirt',925.00,100 );


INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1032','C010','kids1.jpg','D002','Addyvero Girls Midi/Knee Length Party Dress ',450.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1033','C010','kids2.jpg','D002','US Polo Kids Girls Midi/Knee Length Casual Dress',675.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1034','C010','kids3.jpg','D002','Klaud Zee Boys Sherwani and Churidar Set',535.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1035','C010','kids4.jpg','D002','United Colors of Benetton Boys Solid Cotton T Shirt ',910.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1036','C010','kids5.jpg','D002','Adidas Boys Solid T Shirt ',500.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1037','C010','kids6.jpg','D002','Bella Moda Girls Midi/Knee Length Casual Dress ',680.00,100 );

INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1038','C011','shoe1.jpg','D002','Crocs Girls Slip-on Flats Pink ',450.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1039','C011','shoe2.jpg','D002','Cars Boys Slip on Walking Shoes Red ',675.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1040','C011','shoe3.jpg','D002','KITTENS Girls Velcro Flats White  ',910.00,100 );
INSERT INTO Product VALUES('P1041','C011','shoe5.jpg','D002','Puma Boys Lace Football Shoes Black ',500.00,100 );





7.

CREATE TABLE Ship_address
(
user_id  VARCHAR2(15) REFERENCES Users(user_id),
order_id VARCHAR2(10) REFERENCES Orders(order_id),
name varchar2(50) NOT NULL,
phone_no NUMBER(10) NOT NULL,
address1 VARCHAR2(50) NOT NULL,
address2 VARCHAR2(50) NOT NULL,
area varchar2(20),
city varchar2(30) NOT NULL,
state VARCHAR2(20) NOT NULL,
zipcode NUMBER(6) NOT NULL 
)




8.

create table Shop_cart
( 
	product_id varchar2(10) REFERENCES Product(product_id),
	cart_id  varchar2(15) REFERENCES users(user_id),
	quantity Number(10) NOT NULL,
	sub_total Number(10,2) NOT NULL,
	date_added Date DEFAULT SYSDATE,
	CONSTRAINT pro_cart PRIMARY KEY(product_id,cart_id) 
);





9.

CREATE TABLE Orders (
order_id varchar2(10) PRIMARY KEY,
date_ordered date DEFAULT SYSDATE,
date_shipped date DEFAULT SYSDATE,
cust_id varchar2(15) REFERENCES Users(user_id),
status varchar2(30)
)


INSERT INTO Orders VALUES('OR101','25-Sep-2017','28-Sep-2017','geetika_1','confirmed')



10.

CREATE TABLE Order_detail (
order_id varchar2(10) REFERENCES Orders(order_id),
product_id varchar2(10),
quantity number(10),
unit_cost number(10,2),
product_name varchar2(100),
sub_total number(10,2)
)

INSERT INTO Order_detail VALUES('OR101','P101',10,495.50,'Maybelline New York Fit Me Matte + Poreless Foundation',4955.00)



11.

CREATE TABLE Ship_info (
order_id varchar2(10) PRIMARY KEY,
shipping_type varchar2(10),
shipping_cost number(10,2),
zipcode number(10)
)


12.

CREATE table ProductDescription(
               product_id varchar2(10) primary key,
               product_name varchar2(100) not null,
               brief_description varchar2(500) default '--',
               description varchar2(500) default '--',
               brand varchar2(30) default '--',
               type varchar2(50) default '--',
		features varchar2(700) default '--'
);

INSERT 	INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P101','Maybelline New York Fit Me Matte + Poreless Foundation ','Makeup(face)',
'Fit Me Matte + Poreless from Maybelline New York goes beyond skin tone matching to fit the unique texture issues of normal 
to oily skin for the ultimate natural skin fit. While some foundations can exaggerate pores and oily skin, only the FitMe 
Matte+ pore-minimizing foundation contains genius blurring micro-powders that erase pores and absorb oil for a naturally 
matte and poreless-looking finish.','Maybelline New York','Foundation','Tone + texture-fitting foundation for the ultimate 
natural fit<br>This lightweight foundation mattifies and refines pores and leaves a natural, seamless 
finish.<br>Dermatologist and allergy tested.<br>Does not clog pores. Oil-free.<br>Mattifying liquid formula ideal for 
normal to oily skin.<br>Non-comedogenic.')




INSERT 	INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P102','Lakme 9 to 5 Complexion Care CC Cream ','Makeup(face)',
'For women who are on the go and could use the extra minutes before stepping out; Lakme CC cream is here to the rescue. 
This cream acts as your everyday mini skin stylist and lets you get that perfect look of makeup + skincare for any 
occasion. It may be work, party or simply an evening with friends; your personal stylist will help you get the right look 
for it all. It is time to move on to a simpler regime without comprising on skincare. ','Lakme 9 to 5','CC Cream','Provides 
UV Protection.<br>Moisturizes.<br>Conceals.<br>Gives Smooth Coverage.<br>Lightens Skin.<br>Evens skin tone.')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P103','L.A. Girl Pro Conceal HD','Makeup(eye)','With a crease-resistant; opaque coverage in a creamy yet lightweight texture; the L.A. Girl HD Pro Concealer has a long-wearing formula that camouflages darkness under the eyes; redness and skin imperfections.','Maybelline New York','Foundation',' It  evens out skin tone, covers dark circles and minimizes fine lines around the eyes.<br>This blendable and buildable formula provides the ultimate complete and natural-looking customizable coverage.<br> This must-have concealer includes a soft brush-tip for easy application.<br> Try blending a couple of shades together for the perfect match.<br> Apply correctors under regular concealer to create a perfectly even complexion. Complete makeup routine by applying the Highlighter as the last step after foundation.')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P104','Maybelline New York Eye Studio Lasting Drama Gel Eyeliner Black ','Makeup(eye) ','Get the precision of a liquid liner with the ease of a gel-based formula. Add some drama to those eyes with the super-concentrated oil-free gel eyeliner! This waterproof eyeliner has a long-lasting gel formula that achieves dramatic eye looks easily. The eyeliner glides on smoothly and precisely, then quickly dries down to a long-wearing, water-resistant finish. Whether your go thick, thin, smudged, or smoky, your look will last, from day to night. ','Maybelline New York','Eye Liner',' Smudge-free formula sets instantly and glides on easily to deliver intense color that lasts up to 24 hours.<br>
 Long-wearing, water-resistant eyeliner.<br>
 The non-sticky oil free formula glides smoothly and instantly makes your eyes look spectacularly attractive.<br>
 Ophthalmologist tested.<br>
 Dermatologist tested.')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P105','Maybelline New York The 24K Nudes Palette ','Makeup(eye)','The 24K Nudes Eyeshadow Palette features 12 expertly curated shades for custom eye makeup looks. Fashioned for flash! This 12-shade eyeshadow palette features dazzling colors infused with metallic gold pigments. From sparkling gold and shimmering nude to gilded smoke and aubergine spark, this makeup palette is perfect for creating versatile eye looks. ','Maybelline New York','Eye Shadow','12-shade eyeshadow palette.<br>
13 eyeshadow looks with duo, trio, and quad color combinations.<br>
 Infused with sparkling metallic gold pigments. ')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P106','Maybelline New York Volume Express Hyper Curl Mascara ','Makeup(eye) ','Get lusciously curly lashes with the revolutionary Maybelline Volume Express Hyper Curl Mascara. The exclusive curl lock formula gives lengthy expressive lashes for up to 18 hours. With the deepest black color, add instant drama to your eyes, making the simplest of eye makeup, alluring. Get picture perfect curled eyelashes with Maybelline Volume Express Hyper Curl Mascara.','Maybelline New York','Eye Mascara','Curl Lock formula<br>
 Curly eyelashes for 18 hours <br>
 Easy to apply and remove <br>
 Fine texture<br>
 Adds volume<br>
 Anti-clump brush<br>
 Does not smear or smudge')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P107','VLCC Clear Tan Fruits Face Pack ','Skin(face)','VLCC Clear Tan Fruits Face Pack is based upon traditional ayurvedic formulations infused with the essence of Cucumber, Pineapple, Mulberry, and several Ayurvedic herbs. This Face pack reaches deep into the skin cells to nourish and revitalize them. It reduces the signs of sun damage such as sun spots and darkening through natural skin lightening properties and by encouraging new skin growth. ','VLCC','Face Pack','Infused with natural fruit extracts and ayurvedic powder ;face pack is formulated to shield your skin from sun exposure.<br>
  It works as an excellent scrubber and eradicates dirt; excess oil while reducing appearance of fine lines; age spots.<br>
  Provides moisture to the skin to make it soft and smooth.<br>
  Removes tan impressively and leaves you with fairer; lightened up complexion')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P108','Nikon Black Camera','(14MP, 18x Optical Zoom) 3-inch LCD ','14 Megapixels. 18.0 x Optical Zoom. 3.0-inch LCD Screen. Full HD photos and 1280 x 720p HD movie capture. ISO sensitivity ISO6400 at reduced resolution. Tracking Auto Focus. Motion Panorama Mode. Face Detection technology with Blink detection and Smile and shoot mode. 4 x AA batteries not included. WxDxH 110.2 �81.4x73.4mm. Weight 0.341kg (excluding battery and memory card). Weight 0.437kg (including battery and memory card).','Nikon','FinePix S2950HD','14 Megapixels. 18.0 x Optical Zoom. 3.0-inch LCD Screen. Full HD photos and 1280 x 720p HD movie capture. ISO sensitivity ISO6400 at reduced resolution. Tracking Auto Focus. Motion Panorama Mode. Face Detection technology with Blink detection and Smile and shoot mode. 4 x AA batteries not included. WxDxH 110.2 �81.4x73.4mm. Weight 0.341kg (excluding battery and memory card). Weight 0.437kg (including battery and memory card).')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P109','Nikon Red Camera ','(14MP, 18x Optical Zoom) 3-inch LCD','14 Megapixels. 18.0 x Optical Zoom. 3.0-inch LCD Screen. Full HD photos and 1280 x 720p HD movie capture. ISO sensitivity ISO6400 at reduced resolution. Tracking Auto Focus. Motion Panorama Mode. Face Detection technology with Blink detection and Smile and shoot mode. 4 x AA batteries not included. WxDxH 110.2 �81.4x73.4mm. Weight 0.341kg (excluding battery and memory card). Weight 0.437kg (including battery and memory card). ','Nikon','FinePix S2950HD','14 Megapixels. 18.0 x Optical Zoom. 3.0-inch LCD Screen. Full HD photos and 1280 x 720p HD movie capture. ISO sensitivity ISO6400 at reduced resolution. Tracking Auto Focus. Motion Panorama Mode. Face Detection technology with Blink detection and Smile and shoot mode. 4 x AA batteries not included. WxDxH 110.2 �81.4x73.4mm. Weight 0.341kg (excluding battery and memory card). Weight 0.437kg (including battery and memory card).')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1010','DSLR Camera ','(14MP, 18x Optical Zoom) 3-inch LCD ','14 Megapixels. 18.0 x Optical Zoom. 3.0-inch LCD Screen. Full HD photos and 1280 x 720p HD movie capture. ISO sensitivity ISO6400 at reduced resolution. Tracking Auto Focus. Motion Panorama Mode. Face Detection technology with Blink detection and Smile and shoot mode. 4 x AA batteries not included. WxDxH 110.2 �81.4x73.4mm. Weight 0.341kg (excluding battery and memory card). Weight 0.437kg (including battery and memory card). ','Fujifilm','FinePix S2950HD','14 Megapixels. 18.0 x Optical Zoom. 3.0-inch LCD Screen. Full HD photos and 1280 x 720p HD movie capture. ISO sensitivity ISO6400 at reduced resolution. Tracking Auto Focus. Motion Panorama Mode. Face Detection technology with Blink detection and Smile and shoot mode. 4 x AA batteries not included. WxDxH 110.2 �81.4x73.4mm. Weight 0.341kg (excluding battery and memory card). Weight 0.437kg (including battery and memory card).')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1011','DSLR Camera ','(14MP, 18x Optical Zoom) 3-inch LCD','14 Megapixels. 18.0 x Optical Zoom. 3.0-inch LCD Screen. Full HD photos and 1280 x 720p HD movie capture. ISO sensitivity ISO6400 at reduced resolution. Tracking Auto Focus. Motion Panorama Mode. Face Detection technology with Blink detection and Smile and shoot mode. 4 x AA batteries not included. WxDxH 110.2 �81.4x73.4mm. Weight 0.341kg (excluding battery and memory card). Weight 0.437kg (including battery and memory card). ','Fujifilm','FinePix S2950HD','14 Megapixels. 18.0 x Optical Zoom. 3.0-inch LCD Screen. Full HD photos and 1280 x 720p HD movie capture. ISO sensitivity ISO6400 at reduced resolution. Tracking Auto Focus. Motion Panorama Mode. Face Detection technology with Blink detection and Smile and shoot mode. ')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1012','SanDisk SDHC Card 8GB ','SanDisk 8 GB SDHC Class 4 Memory Card ','Compatible with SD or SDHC Supporting Host Devices ','SanDisk','SDHC Card','1. For Mobile, Camera<br>
 2. Capacity: 8 GB<br>
 3. SDHC<br>
 4. Class 4')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1013','SanDisk Extreme Card 16GB ','SanDisk 8 GB SDHC Class 4 Memory Card ','Brand New 95MB/s Read Speed 633X SanDisk Extreme PRO� 16GB SDXC UHS-I U3 Class 10 Flash Memory Card 4K ULTRA HD U3 P/N: SDSDXPA-16G-G46 (Sealed RETAIL PACK) Read Speed up to 95 Mb/s 633X Write Speed up to 90Mb/s 600X SanDisk Extreme PRO SDXC UHS-I Memory Card (16 GB) Whether you are in the studio or out in the field, SanDisk Extreme PRO SDHC UHS-I U3 Memory Cards are an ideal storage solution for professional photographers and videographers. Offering read speeds up to 95 MB/s. ','SanDisk','SDHC Card','1. For Camera<br>
 2. Capacity: 16 GB<br>
 3. SDXC<br>
 4. Class 10<br>
 5. Read Speed: 95 MB/s')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1014','Van Heusen White Dress ','Women Dresses ','Color :White ','Van Heusen','Dress','Fit :Regular<br> 
 Material :100% Polyester ')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1015','Van Heusen Womens Regular Fit Dress','Women Dresses ','Color :Blue ','Van Heusen','Dress','1.Material :100% Cotton<br>
 2.Biker dress <br>
 3.Beautifully crafted<br>
 4.Well constructed <br>
 5.Quality fabrics ')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1016','Van Heusen Womens Regular Fit Dress','Women Dresses ','Color :Grey ','Van Heusen','Dress','1.Material :100% Cotton<br> 
 2.Biker dress <br>
 3.Beautifully crafted<br>
 4.Well constructed <br>
 5.Quality fabrics ')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1017','Vero Moda Womens Solid Sleeveless High
 Neck ','Women Dresses ','Color :Black ','Vero Moda','Dress','1.Material :100% Cotton<br> 
 2.Biker dress <br>
 3.Beautifully crafted<br>
 4.Well constructed <br>
 5.Quality fabrics ')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1018','Vero Moda Womens Solid Sleeveless Loose Fit V Neck Casual dress','Women Dresses ','Color :Brown','Vero Moda','Dress','1.Material :100% Cotton 
 2.Biker dress 
 3.Beautifully crafted
 4.Well constructed 
 5.Quality fabrics  ')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1019','Griffel Solid Mens 
Track Suit','Men Sportswear','Griffel MenS High Quality Fleece Tracksuit','Griffel','Tracksuit','Mens<br>
 Pattern: Solid<br>
 Fabric: Material : Polyster Cotton ')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1020','Bsquare Snapback
 Cap ','Men Sportswear','Bsquare Snapback Cap','Bsquare','Cap','Mens Cap<br>
 Type: Snapback<br>
 Fabric: cotton ')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1021','Alan Jones Solid Mens Black 
Track Pants','Men Sportswear','We are crushing on joggers this season, especially this pair ! Pick these mens joggers and flaunt a cool and casual style. Kick back and relax in style with these comfy must-have essentials. Pair them with a printed vest or a casual shirt depending on the occasion and show off your style -icon worty style. ','Alan','Lower','Ideal For: Mens<br>
 Fabric: Cotton<br>
 Pattern: Solid<br>
 Usage: Sportswear')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1022','Maniac Solid Mens Dark Blue
 Track Pants ','Men Sportswear','Loop knitted navy coloured track pant from the house of Maniac will be a great addition to your sportswear collection. Made from breathable cotton fabric,it has two pocekts at the either side and an elasticated waistband for comfortable fit.These track pant will keep you fresh and dry all day long. ','Maniac','Lower','Ideal For: Mens<br>
 Fabric: Cotton<br>
 Pattern: Solid<br>
 Usage: Sportswear, Sleepwear ')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1023','Lotto Solid Mens Grey 
Track Pants','Men Sportswear','This model has a height of 6 feet 0 inches and is wearing a of Size ','Lotto','Lower','Ideal For: Mens<br>
 Fabric: 100% Cotton<br>
 Pattern: Solid<br>
 Usage: Sportswear ')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1024','Black printed casual shirt ','Men Shirt','This model has a height of 6 feet 0 inches and is wearing a of Size ','Van Heusen ','Men clothing',
'Ideal For: Mens<br>
 Fabric: 100% Cotton<br>')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1025','Green and black woven printed casual shirt ','Men Shirt','This model has a height of 6 feet 0 inches and is wearing a of Size ','Van Heusen ','Men clothing',
'Ideal For: Mens<br>
 Fabric: 100% Cotton<br>')
INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1026','Off-white and navy blue printed casual shirt ','Men Shirt','This model has a height of 6 feet 0 inches and is wearing a of Size ','Van Heusen ','Men clothing',
'Ideal For: Mens<br>
 Fabric: 100% Cotton<br>')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1027','Blue solid formal shirt  ','Men Shirt','This model has a height of 6 feet 0 inches and is wearing a of Size ','Van Heusen ','Men clothing',
'Ideal For: Mens<br>
 Fabric: 100% Cotton<br>')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1028','Brown and navy blue checked formal shirt ','Men Shirt','This model has a height of 6 feet 0 inches and is wearing a of Size ','Louis Philippe ','Men clothing',
'Ideal For: Mens<br>
 Fabric: 100% Cotton<br>')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1029','Black and grey checked formal shirt ','Men Shirt','This model has a height of 6 feet 0 inches and is wearing a of Size ','Louis Philippe ','Men clothing',
'Ideal For: Mens<br>
 Fabric: 100% Cotton<br>')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1030','Blue and white checked casual shirt ','Men Shirt','This model has a height of 6 feet 0 inches and is wearing a of Size ','Louis Philippe ','Men clothing',
'Ideal For: Mens<br>
 Fabric: 100% Cotton<br>')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1031','White pink and blue checked casual shirt','Men Shirt','This model has a height of 6 feet 0 inches and is wearing a of Size ','Louis Philippe ','Men clothing',
'Ideal For: Mens<br>
 Fabric: 100% Cotton<br>')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1032','Addyvero Girls Midi/Knee Length Party Dress ','Casual wear','Offering the best of style and comfort, this dress will be an ideal pick for your little one.',
'Addyvero','Kids Clothing','Fabric: Cotton Linen Blend')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1033','US Polo Kids Girls Midi/Knee Length Casual Dress','Casual wear','Offering the best of style and comfort, this dress will be an ideal pick for your little one.','US Polo','Kids Clothing','Fabric: Cotton Linen Blend')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1034','Klaud Zee Boys Sherwani and Churidar Set','ethnic wear','Offering the best of style and comfort, this dress will be an ideal pick for your little one.',
'Klaud Zee','Kids Clothing','Fabric: Cotton Linen Blend')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1035','United Colors of Benetton Boys Solid Cotton T Shirt ','Casual wear','Offering the best of style and comfort, this dress will be an ideal pick for your little one.',
'United Colors of Benetton','Kids Clothing','Fabric: Cotton Linen Blend')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1036','Adidas Boys Solid T Shirt ','Casual wear','Offering the best of style and comfort, this dress will be an ideal pick for your little one.',
'Adidas','Kids Clothing','Fabric: Cotton Linen Blend')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1037','Bella Moda Girls Midi/Knee Length Casual Dress ','Casual wear','Offering the best of style and comfort, this dress will be an ideal pick for your little one.',
'Bella Moda','Kids Clothing','Fabric: Cotton Linen Blend')


INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1038','Crocs Girls Slip-on Flats Pink ','Girls Footwear','Stylish Light In Weight And Soft From Base This Casual Sandal Is Perfect For Your Li L Angel.',
'Crocs','Kids Shoes','Ideal For: Girls')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1039','Cars Boys Slip on Walking Shoes Red ','Boys Footwear','Stylish Light In Weight And Soft From Base This Casual Sandal Is Perfect For Your LiL Angel.',
'Cars Boys','Kids Shoes',Ideal For: Boys')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1040','KITTENS Girls Velcro Flats White  ','Girls Footwear','Stylish Light In Weight And Soft From Base This Casual Sandal Is Perfect For Your LiL Angel.',
'KITTENS','Kids Shoes','Ideal For: Girls')

INSERT INTO ProductDescription VALUES('P1041','Puma Boys Lace Football Shoes Black ','Boys Footwear','Stylish Light In Weight And Soft From Base This Casual Sandal Is Perfect For Your LiL Angel.',
'Puma','Kids Shoes','Ideal For: Girls')





